我回来了  嘿
Hi, you guys. Hey.
怎么了
What's the matter?
又是那种很讨厌的状况
Well, it's just... It's one of these situations that I just hate.
有一个客人送我三张票
You know, a massage client gave me three tickets...
是去摩根大通博物馆看展览的
...to the Helmut Peltz Exhibit at the Morgan Chase Museum.
所以  你觉得你得陪他睡觉
Now you're thinking you gotta sleep with him.
不  不是  他只给了三张票  但是我们有六个人
No. No, it's just that he gave me three tickets and there are six of us.
我弃权  我也是
I'll give up my ticket. Me too.
你们真大方
Okay. That's so generous.
罗斯也应该很大方的
And I think Ross is generous too.
太好了  就我们女生去
Great. Okay. Then it's just us girls.
很棒  对
Great. Yeah.
那个  是什么展览
So, what is the exhibit?
主要是图片展
It's mostly just photographs...
女同的性爱摄影展  视频游戏  送免费三明治
...of, um, lesbian love scenes interspersed with video games and free sandwiches.
都是你
Oh, man.
大家好  嘿
Hi. Hi. Hi there.
嘿  罗斯  听着
Hey, Ross, listen.
钱德刚把你周末去女同三明治博物馆的机会给让出去了
Chandler got you out of going to the lesbian sandwich museum this weekend.
谢谢   我另有安排了  伊丽莎白和我要出城去
Thanks? But I have plans. Uh, Elizabeth and I are going out of town.
太好了  对啊
Oh, that's great. Yeah.
你要发财了
Think about all the money that you're gonna make.
什么意思
Why? What?
是她爸付钱请你当保姆  对吧
Well, her father pays you for babysitting, right?
哇哦
Uh-oh. Ha, ha.
不  真好笑   是不是该放我们一马了
No, no. That's funny. But maybe it's time to move on.
够了  别再闹了  不许再提
You know, let it go. Stop it.
再说了   瑞秋不是也在和她爸交往嘛
Besides, Rachel's going out with Elizabeth's father.
而且他比瑞秋老太多了
So, uh, he's much older than she is.
看来不只是我对化石有兴趣啊
Looks like I'm not the only one interested in fossils. Huh?
罗斯  这种话只会提醒我们  你的确对化石有兴趣
I means, all that does is remind us that you are interested in fossils.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
嗯  以后瑞秋想和他甜言蜜语   要大吼大叫了
Uh, well, Rachel's gonna to need to yell sweet nothings in his ear. Huh?
罗斯  拜托  难道你们不觉得好笑
Ross? Oh, come on, that's funny, you know?
他需要戴助听器了
he's need— he's got, like, a hearing aide, you know?
因为他太老了
‘cause-‘cause y'know, ‘cause he's all old.
失陪一下
One second.
听着  罗斯
Okay, look, Ross.
因为丽莎很喜欢你
Just so you know, since Lizzie likes you so much...
所以我决定接受你们交往的事实
...I accept the fact that you're going out with her.
真的  那太好了
Really? Okay, that's great.
是啊  但现在我改主意了
Yeah. But then I changed my mind.
我就是这么善变
I'm funny like that.
我已经警告了丽莎   现在我警告你
So I've told Lizzie and now I'm telling you.
不许再跟我女儿见面了
I don't want you seeing my daughter anymore.
好吧   我知道你很不满意
All right, look. I realize it upsets you.
没错  很不满意
Yes, it does.
但丽莎和我都是成年人了
But Elizabeth and I are both adults...
所以我想  你也无可奈何
...and so I don't think there's really anything you can do about it.
我会告诉校方   让师生恋曝光   你就会被开除
I'll tell the university about your relationship and have you fired.
有备而来啊
Oh, a man with a plan.
老友记  第六季  第22集  大逆转
Friends  S06E22  The One Where Paul's The Man
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
太帅了   你的照片又重返名人墙了
This is so exciting. You get your picture back up on the wall of fame.
是啊  之前贴在墙上好酷啊
I know. It was so cool when it was up there before.
我经常和吉姆贝路西有说有笑
Me and Jim Belushi would just be cracking up about something.
后来我被《我们的日子》开除   照片就被拿下来
Then I get fired off Days of Our Lives and he takes me down.
到现在他都在嘲笑我
Now he's just laughing at me.
你看那个  自呜得意的混蛋
Look at him. That smug Belushi bastard.
也许他们可以   把你挂在
Oh. Okay. Maybe when they put your picture back up...
麦特劳尔旁边
...they could put you next to Matt Lauer.
你看他在冲我微笑
Look at him just smiling at me. Hee-hee.
我知道   我们俩一定合拍
Yeah, I know. We'd be great together.
我回来了  你是谁
Hey. So I'm back. Who are you?
乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
之前上过名人墙的
From the wall?
也许这样   你会想起来
Okay, maybe this will jog your memory, huh?
嗯
Huh?
总之
Okay, anyway.
我可以返回墙上了  我主演了一出新戏
I'm ready to go back up on the wall. I'm the star of a new TV show.
翻给我看   还没演呢
Show me in the TV book. Oh, well, it's not on TV yet.
那你就不能上墙了
Well, then it's not on the wall yet.
这样吧   我拿录影带给你看  可以吧
Okay, fine. I will bring you a tape. Huh?
你手边有麦特劳尔的衣服吗
So, um, now, do you have any of Matt Lauer's clothes here?
或许还有没洗过的
Maybe just ones that haven't been cleaned yet?
天啊
God.
哦  我好喜欢到博物馆
Oh, I love museums.
来接受文化薰陶
Soaking up all the culture. Yeah.
你想先去哪里   去礼品部
Where do you want to start? Ooh, the gift shop.
好啊
Yeah.
然后去用餐   等等  我不能吃太多
Hey, and then lunch. Oh, wait, yes, but I can't eat too much.
保罗今晚要带我去吃饭   他说会有个大惊喜
Paul's taking me out to dinner tonight. He said he has a big surprise planned.
他会不会告诉你说  他是个同性恋
Ow, wow. What do you think? Maybe he's gonna tell you he's gay?
什么啊  不可能  你为什么这么说
What? No, why?
不为什么   这样才真是个大惊喜啊
No reason. That would just be a really big surprise, right?
红毯可以铺在这边   然后在这边举办婚礼仪式
You could put the aisle over here and then have the wedding ceremony here.
原来这里可以办婚礼
I didn't know you could get married here.
作为婚礼场所   这里太美了
This would be a beautiful place to get married.
但我不会把红毯铺在那边   更不会在那边举办婚礼仪式
Yeah, but I wouldn't put the aisle there. And I'd never have the ceremony there.
应该在这个漂亮的拱门下宣誓
You'd have the ceremony under this big, beautiful arch.
有什么事吗
May I help you?
抱歉打断你   这地方太美了
Oh, sorry. Didn't mean to interrupt. It's just such a beautiful space.
常办婚礼吗  是的  这里很受欢迎
Do you do a lot of weddings here? Yes, we're very popular.
预约都已经排到两年后了   抱歉
There's a two-year waiting list. Sorry.
摩妮卡  你也应该去报名预约
Monica, you should totally put your name down for this place.
什么   你疯了吗
What? Are you crazy?
我又不结婚   甚至还没订婚
I'm not getting married. I'm not even engaged.
对啊   反正要等两年嘛   要是你两年内订了婚才报名
Yeah, but there's a two-year wait. What if you get engaged in two years?
不是还得再等两年才能在这里办嘛
Then you've gotta wait another two years for this place?
加起来就四年了   钱德才不会等那么久
That's four years. Chandler's not gonna wait that long.
他会去找别人了
He's gonna find somebody else, you know?
找某个预约报了名的女人
Someone, someone who did put their name on the list. Mm-hm.
亲爱的  先预约又不会怎样
Yeah. Honey, it can't hurt to put your name down.
要是两年内没订婚   就放弃不用了
If in two years you're not engaged, you just don't use it.
有道理   先预约的确不会怎样
Well, I guess there is no harm in putting my name down.
我也要预约   我也要
I'm gonna do it too. Me too.
真的  你要嫁给谁
Really? Who would you marry?
不知道   我现在还没有对象
I don't know. I don't have anyone right now, you know?
噢  菲比
Oh, Pheebs.
别为我难过  至少我的男朋友不是同性恋
Don't feel too sorry for me. At least my boyfriend isn't gay.
菲比  这种事  别招惹我批评你家那个啊
Phoebe, that's not... Don't even get me started on yours.
嘿
Hey.
看过我拿来的带子了吗   看过了
So, did you watch the tape of my show? I did.
怎样  我能上墙了吗  不行  你不能上墙
All right. Let's get me back up there. No. You don't go up on the wall.
什么  但你是看了我的片子  对  你那片子冒犯了我们
What? But you saw the show. Yes. It was very offensive to my people.
冒犯了干洗店一族
Dry cleaners?
冒犯了俄国人   把他们都当成恐怖分子和恶棍
Russians. It showed them as terrorists and villains.
好  你看  你墙上还有哈里逊福特
Okay, okay. Look, you got Harrison Ford up there.
没错   福特先生是个好顾客
That's right. Mr. Ford is a very good customer.
他能带很多衣服来洗  而你却两手空空
He brings us a lot of clothes. You bring us nothing.
说得也许对
Okay, well, that may be true.
但《空军一号》里   俄国人是恐怖分子  很邪恶
But, in-in .Air Force One. okay, the Russians  were terrorists and evil.
他还杀了一堆俄国人  那才是冒犯俄国人呢
And plus, he kills a bunch of them. That's offensive to Russians.
我没看过  你应该要看  很赞
I've never seen it. Oh, you should. It's great.
这里真的好漂亮
This place is really beautiful.
对啊  我从小就常来  这里以前是我奶奶家
Yeah. I've been coming here since I was a kid. This used to be my grandma's.
可我只遗传了我奶奶的眼睛
Wow. The only thing I got from my grandmother was her eyes. Heh.
我不是说她的眼珠子
I mean, not her actual eyeballs.
但大家都说我的眼睛长得像
But people say that my eyes look...
你要不要亲热   要啊  好啊
Do you want to make out? Sure. Ha, ha.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
怎么了
What's wrong? Uh...
我只是想起了你爸爸
Yeah, I was just thinking about your father.
只要能让你兴奋就好  不是
Well, whatever works for you. No.
不  不  不是  是他有点把我吓到了
No, no. Uh, he just really freaked me out before.
哦
Oh.
那我们还得再多瞒着一个人
Well, so we have to hide our relationship from one more person.
那又怎样  而且  我们也喜欢这样偷偷摸摸着玩
Big deal. Besides, we've had fun hiding it.
也对
Yeah.
嘿   嗯
Hey. Yeah.
你有带防护用具吗
Um, you brought protection, right?
怎么了  这里有熊出没吗
Why? Are there, like, bears or something?
不是  那个
No. Oh, uh...
你是说那个  没有  我简直忘了
Oh, protection, yeah. No. That I forgot.
那我赶快去商店里买
Ha, ha. I'll just run to the store and get some.
不   嘿  我是男人  应该我去买
No. Hey, hey. I'm the guy. I'll get it.
你知道商店在哪里   不知道
Do you know where the store is? No.
那你想骑我粉红脚踏车满城转悠吗
Do you want to ride around town on my little pink bicycle?
有点想
A little bit.
我十分钟后回来  好
I'll be back in 10 minutes. Okay.
那不如你先泡个热澡   在浴缸里等我
Why don't you get in the hot tub and I'll meet you there.
好
Oh, okay.
天哪   好棒的惊喜  这房子真漂亮
Oh, my God. What a great surprise. This is such a beautiful house.
谢谢   这是我妈的房子  这里是厨房
Thank you. It used to be my mother's. So this is the kitchen.
这边是摩妮卡和钱德的家
You've reached Monica and Chandler's.
如果你听到这则留言   我们也许正在监听
If you're listening to this message, we're probably screening.
没错
Yeah, we are.
我是摩根大通博物馆的希蒂
Hi, this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
我要找摩妮卡盖勒
I'm calling for Monica Geller.
有客人取消了预约
I want to let her know there was a cancellation.
如果她还想在我们这里办婚礼
If she's still interested in having the Bing-Geller wedding at our facility...
现在有空了
...it is available.
我是钱德宾  我是钱德宾
This is Chandler Bing. This is Chandler Bing.
是的  我是新郎  不  我不是
Yes, the groom. No, not the groom!
这里好幽静
It's so secluded up here.
对   所以我喜欢这里
I know. That's why I like it here. Mm-hm.
好像全世界就只剩我们两个人
I feel like we're the only two people in the world.
抱歉
Whoops. Sorry.
怎么了   宝贝
What's the matter, honey?
你看到一只小老鼠了吗  不是  是大熊  外面有大熊
Did you see a little mouse? No. Big bear. Big bear outside.
我想我
I think I...
你要不要   要不要处去查看一下
Actually, would you go check on that?
亲爱的   这里没有熊出没
Honey, we don't have any bears here.
好吧
Well, okay.
帮我倒杯健怡可乐
Well, okay. Would-would you get me a Diet Coke?
好  马上回来   好
Okay. I'll be right back. Okay.
你在这里干嘛   你又在这里干嘛
What are you doing here? What are you doing here?
我是跟保罗来的   我认得出他的脚踝
I came with Paul. Yeah. I recognized the ankles.
快点   滚出来
Hurry up. Get out.
拿来了   宝贝
Here you go, honey.
谢谢你   健怡可乐
Ah. Thank you. Diet Coke.
冰块
Oh. Ice.
我要加冰块
I need ice.
好
Okay.
谢谢你   我马上回来
Thank you. Be right back.
好
Okay.
又是冰块这一招
You and your ice. Oh.
出来   出来   快点
Get out. Get out. Go. Come on.
快点
Quick.
不行  不行  别去  他在那里面
No, not in there! Not in there! He's in there!
你真的听到熊叫了吗   快跑
Did you really hear a bear? Go!
来了  宝贝
Here you go, honey.
加冰的健怡可乐
One Diet Coke with ice.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
真高兴有你在
I am so happy that you're here.
我回来了  伊丽莎白
Here I am. Elizabeth.
看   伊丽莎白来了
Oh, look. Elizabeth's here.
你在跟谁说话
Who were you talking to?
你们啊
You guys?
你怎么知道我们来了
How did you know we were here?
她一定是看到
Um... Well, she obviously saw the tire tracks...
车库的方向有轮胎印
...that were leading up to the closed garage.
没错
Obviously. Heh.
伊丽莎白   你来这里干什么
Elizabeth, what are you doing here?
你是来这里赶报告的吗
Did you come up here to work on that term paper or something?
没错
Yeah. Yeah.
不如你去那个房间写吧
Well, why don't you, you know, go in that room and do your homework?
不去   那是我爸的卧房
Oh, I wouldn't do it in there. Um, that's my dad's bedroom.
那是你爸的卧房
That's your dad's bedroom.
Ha, ha. That's your dad's bedroom.
你干嘛这么大声
Why are you yelling? Oh!
可乐起作用了  让我好嗨
That Diet Coke, I think, went straight to my head. Whoo!
嗨  亲爱的
Hi, honey.
待会儿见
See you later.
我买了东西   正想给你做饭呢
Wait. I bought groceries. I was gonna make you dinner.
那下次先问我
Well, next time, ask.
或等我先开口问
Or at least wait for me to ask.
我是摩根大通博物馆的希蒂
Hi, this is Hildy from the Morgan Chase Museum.
我要找摩妮卡盖勒
I'm calling for Monica Geller.
完了
Oh, no.
有客人取消预约
I wanna let her know there's been a cancellation.
如果她还想在我们这里办婚礼
If she's still interested in having the Bing-Geller wedding at our facility...
现在有空了
...it is available.
拜托  他没听到  他没听到
Please. He didn't hear it. He didn't hear it.
我是钱德宾  我是钱德宾
This is Chandler Bing. This is Chandler Bing.
不
No!
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
负责上名人墙的那家伙呢
Uh, yeah. Where's the guy who decides whose pictures go up on the wall?
他现在不在  不会吧
He's not here right now. Oh, you're kidding me.
你务必告诉他   乔伊崔比亚尼带了一堆衣服来洗
All right, well, make sure you tell him that Joey Tribbiani stopped by to drop off these clothes.
我是个演员   我想让我的照片上名人墙
Okay? I'm an actor. I'm trying to get my picture up there on the wall.
其实吧   有两个人有权利决定这事
You know, there are two people who could get your picture up there.
真的吗
Oh, really?
要不我们出去喝一杯
Well, maybe you and I go out for drinks.
你就是那另外两个   对吧
You're the other one, right?
丽莎   你今晚要留下来过夜吗
So, Lizzie, are-are-are you planning on staying the night?
不  不  我要尽快离开
Oh, no, no. Believe me, I'm leaving as soon as possible.
那就好  不是我们赶你走啊  显然  你很受欢迎
Good, good. Not that we don't want you to stay. Obviously, you're welcome.
你还有多少功课
How much more homework do you have?
只剩一个问题   我不知道怎么解决
Uh, I just have one problem left that I do not know how to solve.
瑞秋   也许你可以上楼来帮我
Uh, Rachel, maybe you want to come upstairs and help me figure it out?
真的吗
Really?
好
Okay.
好  我上楼
Okay, I'll go upstairs...
你去车上帮我拿东西
...if you get me something from the car.
你要拿什么东西
What do you need from the car?
给我惊喜啊
Surprise me.
好   好啊
Okay. Okay.
你要去车上   我上楼
So you're gonna be in the car. I will be upstairs.
这里就空无一人了
And that's where everybody's gonna be.
放轻松  放轻松  保罗  你表现得很好
Just relax. Just relax, Paul. You're doing great.
她喜欢你
She likes you. She...
我想她喜欢你   她喜欢你
I think she likes you. She likes you.
为什么   因为你爱干净
You know why? Because you're a neat guy.
你是男子汉   你是男子汉
You are the man. You are the man.
魅力不减当年
Still got it.
还很性感
Still sexy.
你是一个爱情机器
You're just a love machine.
我是一个爱情机器
I'm just a love machine
为你所拥有的而自豪   宝贝
So proud of what you have, baby
上场了
Showtime.
我是一个爱情机器   宝贝
I'm just a love machine Hey, baby
菲比  什么事
Phoebe? Yeah?
看见到钱德吗   没有   怎么了
Have you seen Chandler? No, why?
博物馆那个女人来电话说   有客人取消预约
The woman from the museum called and said that there was a cancellation...
我们可以提前举行婚礼了   电话被钱德听见了
...and we could move up our wedding. and Chandler heard.
我知道这有严重
I know. How bad is this?
对普通男人来说很严重  但是对钱德  我的天哪
Well, with a regular guy, it's bad. With Chandler, oh, dear God.
我知道  他被吓得落荒而逃  人都没影了
I know. I know. He totally freaked out and I can't find him anywhere.
那你怎么办   反正我再也不听你的话了
Well, what are you gonna do? I'm never listening to you again, that's for sure!
"先预约又不会怎样"
"Y'know, harm can it do to put your name down?"
那是瑞秋说的   瑞秋不在这里
Rachel said that. Well, Rachel's not here!
在这里
Ooh, here it is.
乔伊   你为什么要签 "混蛋"
Ooh, Joey, why did you sign it, "son of a bitch"?
（混蛋）
我没有啊   这是谁干的   混蛋
I didn't do that. Who would've done that? Son of a bitch.
问问他好了
Okay. Maybe ask this guy.
你  滚出我的店
You. Get out of my shop.
他做什么坏事了  他跟我老婆约会
What did he do? He went out with my wife.
乔伊
Joey. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
什么啊   我没有跟你老婆约会   好吗
Hey, I did not go out with your wife. Okay?
我是跟她约会   她就是我老婆
I went out with her. That's my wife.
滚
Get out!
我们还是走好了  对
Well, we should go. Yeah.
罗斯  罗斯
Ross? Ross?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
好了   我从窗户爬出去
Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go out this window.
我们前门见
I'll meet you at the front door.
你就说你要回家  好
Just tell them you're going home, okay? Okay.
等等   等等   先别进去
Wait, wait. No, don't go in there.
先别进去  我还要喝汽水
Don't go in there. I need another soda.
罗斯
Ross.
天哪   罗斯  你在这里干什么
Oh, my God. Ross, what in heaven's name are you doing here?
所以  我们还是不要再见面了
And that is why we cannot see each other anymore.
罗斯   我们得好好谈一谈了
Ross, you and I are gonna have to have a little talk.
爸   接着就是你
Daddy, I... You're next.
好  我不知道他来了
Okay. I didn't know he was here.
让我把话问清楚
Let me just see if I got this straight.
我叫你要么离我女儿远一点  要么我要学校开除你
I tell you to stay away from my daughter or I'll have you fired.
结果你听到的是  "带我女儿
What you heard was: "Take my daughter...
到我乡下的别墅   坏我和瑞秋的好事"
...come up to my country house and ruin my weekend with Rachel."
拜托  请听我解释  不  你听我解释  开除
Okay. Please, Paul. Just let me explain. No. Let me explain. Fired.
好  开除就开除
Okay, fine. Fine. Have me fired.
但我想让你知道
But, uh, I want you to know...
你跟我并没区别   我意思
...that you and I are not all that different. I mean...
我也爱干净
...l, too, am a neat guy.
什么
What?
我也是
And I, too...
一个爱情机器
...am just a love machine.
罗斯
Ross.
我带你去客房
Let me show you where the guest room is.
对不起   你别怕
I'm so sorry. Please stop freaking out.
我不怕啊
I'm not freaking out.
有什么好怕的
Why would I freak out?
有个叫希蒂的女人打电话来说   我们要结婚了
A woman named Hildy called and said we were getting married.
但这很平常啊
But that happens every day. Ah-ah-ah!
亲爱的  那个地方很漂亮
Honey, we were at this beautiful place.
我只是觉得预约多好玩的
And I just put our names down for fun.
也不会怎么样的嘛   是吗
I mean, what's the harm in that? Right here.
钱德   千万别以为我想逼婚
Chandler, please don't think I was trying to pressure you.
菲比和瑞秋觉得   菲比和瑞秋
Phoebe and Rachel just thought... Phoebe and Rachel?
所以她们比我早知道   我们要结婚的
So the people that knew about our wedding before me were you...
菲比和瑞秋   希蒂
...Phoebe and Rachel, Hildy...
和一个叫《星光魔力》的乐团都先知道的
...and apparently some band called Star Light Magic Seven...
只有他们有空
...who are available, by the way.
是我错了
It was a mistake.
这没什么意义   别当真
Please don't take this to mean anything, because it doesn't.
好吧
Okay.
真的吗
Really?
如果你真的没有那个意思  你知道的我也还没准备好
Yes. If it really doesn't mean anything, because you know I'm just not ready.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
好
Okay.
All right.
我去告诉乔伊你回来了
Now, I'm gonna go tell Joey that you're back.
我们刚才好担心
We were really worried about you.
她信了吗   确信无疑
Hey, did she buy it? Totally.
希蒂有带你参观场地了吗  有  美仑美奂
So did Hildy show you the place? Yeah. It's beautiful.
你居然要跟摩妮卡求婚了
I can't believe you're gonna ask Monica to marry you.
就是啊
I know.
阿甘  把这些卡布奇诺瑞到11号桌
Hey, Gunther. Take these cappuccinos to Table 11.
那个男的点了小甜饼
And that guy over there wants some biscotti.
我只是要外带一杯咖啡
Oh. Well, I just actually came in for a cup of coffee to go.
你还在这里上班吗
Do you still work here?
没有  我早就不做了
No, no. I quit a long time ago.
我忘了通知你   抱歉
Did I forget to tell you that? I'm sorry.
算了  反正我也打算开除你  太好了
Oh, that's cool, I was gonna fire you anyway. Great.